import db from ".";

const seedData = async () => {
  const existingStory1 = await db.decks.where("name").equals("Story1").first();

  if (existingStory1) {
    console.log("Decks already exist. Skipping seeding.");
    return;
  }

  let deckId1;
  if (!existingStory1) {
    deckId1 = await db.decks.add({ name: "Story1" });

    const story1cards = [
      {
        front: "Horseman",
        back: "Jinete",
        emoji: "🐴",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },

      {
        front: "Headless",
        back: "Sin cabeza",
        emoji: "💀",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "who",
        back: "Quién",
        emoji: "👥",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "What",
        back: "Qué",
        emoji: "🤔",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "There is",
        back: "Hay",
        emoji: "📍",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },

      {
        front: "He has",
        back: "Él tiene",
        emoji: "👫",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Problem",
        back: "Problema",
        emoji: "🤕",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "He goes",
        back: "Él va",
        emoji: "🚶‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "To the doctor",
        back: "Al doctor",
        emoji: "👨‍⚕️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Ask(s)",
        back: "Pregunta",
        emoji: "💬",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Your",
        back: "Tu",
        emoji: "👉",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "He says",
        back: "Él dice",
        emoji: "👄",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "I have",
        back: "Yo tengo",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Big",
        back: "Grande",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "House",
        back: "Casa",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Rich",
        back: "Rico",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Man",
        back: "Hombre",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Billion",
        back: "Mil millones",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Can you help me?",
        back: "¿Puedes ayudarme?",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "I cannot help",
        back: "No puedo ayudar",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "I can help",
        back: "Puedo ayudar",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Small",
        back: "Pequeño",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Animals",
        back: "Animales",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
    ];

    const story1cardsEnglish = [
      {
        front: "Kim",
        back: "Who",
        emoji: "👥",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Nima",
        back: "What",
        emoji: "🤔",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Bor",
        back: "There is",
        emoji: "📍",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Boshsiz",
        back: "Headless",
        emoji: "💀",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Chavandoz",
        back: "Horseman",
        emoji: "🐴",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Unda bor",
        back: "He has",
        emoji: "👫",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Problema",
        back: "Problem",
        emoji: "🤕",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "U bor(adi)",
        back: "He go(es)",
        emoji: "🚶‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Doktor(ga)",
        back: "(to) the doctor",
        emoji: "👨‍⚕️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Sora(ydi)",
        back: "Ask(s)",
        emoji: "💬",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Sizning",
        back: "Your",
        emoji: "👉",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "U de(ydi)",
        back: "He say(s)",
        emoji: "👄",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Menda bor",
        back: "I have",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Katta",
        back: "Big",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Uy",
        back: "House",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Boy",
        back: "Rich",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Odam, erkak",
        back: "Man",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Milliard",
        back: "Billion",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Yordam bera olasizmi menga?",
        back: "Can you help me?",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Yordam bera olmayman",
        back: "I cannot help",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Yordam bera olaman",
        back: "I can help",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Kichkina",
        back: "Small",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
      {
        front: "Hayvonlar",
        back: "Animals",
        emoji: "🙋‍♂️",
        deckId: deckId1,
        interval: 0,
        repetition: 0,
        easeFactor: 2.5,
        nextReviewDate: null,
      },
    ];

    await db.cards.bulkAdd(story1cards);
  }

  console.log("Sample decks and cards added");
};

export default seedData;
